const grade1data=[
    {
        question:"hypothesis",
        choices:["実体","括弧","強調","仮説"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"archaeological",
        choices:["考古学の","人類学の","地質学の","生物学の"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"bribery",
        choices:["強盗","窃盗","贈収賄","偽証"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"nourishment",
        choices:["看護","栄養","飼育","処罰"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"dissent",
        choices:["不和","不満","異議","解雇"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"pull off",
        choices:["辞退する","取り壊す","成功する","後退する"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"settle on",
        choices:["決定する","満足する","定住する","精算する"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"gain on",
        choices:["獲得する","追いつく","味方にする","回復する"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"mark out",
        choices:["区画する","値下げする","書き留める","注釈をつける"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"draw in",
        choices:["引き出す","作成する","勧誘する","活用する"],
        answer:2
    }
]

export default grade1data;